{
    "id": "61c4387480bc46209ba1346214c4aa77",
    "title": "Question Tags Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "You never say what you want, ………………………?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "do you",
                "don't you",
                "have you",
                "haven't you"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "c1f13d930bd74a9ba668cea3d9a6a071"
        },
        {
            "question": "I am late, ……………………?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "am I",
                "amn't I",
                "aren't I"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "609a0c8384c44dfea3db071e0932bf23"
        },
        {
            "question": "She has a daughter, …………………..?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "has she",
                "hasn't she",
                "does she"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "0978aede5e19463aaa94f7d9615829da"
        },
        {
            "question": "Nobody phoned, …………………...?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "did they",
                "didn't they",
                "had they"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "bad33d2b641340b38717365e2a74ea9c"
        },
        {
            "question": "There is little we can do about it, ……………………?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "is there",
                "isn't there",
                "has there"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "beb63f7ead26478db2783d739eaad94a"
        },
        {
            "question": "Nothing happened, …………………..?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "did they",
                "did it",
                "didn't they"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "a96d7db71ce34427871a6364c258dd7f"
        },
        {
            "question": "They have hardly any money, ………………………?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "have they",
                "haven't they",
                "don't they"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "33a550df96ab4174b2a7d3ec640bc138"
        },
        {
            "question": "Let’s watch a movie, …………………..?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "let we",
                "do we",
                "can we",
                "shall we"
            ],
            "correct": 3,
            "id": "2163684875494b80912f55a6e4ad5b4a"
        },
        {
            "question": "Somebody wanted a ticket, …………………?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "did they",
                "didn't they",
                "had they"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "6a7e2090d5cb4134b19dce7a2271f71f"
        },
        {
            "question": "You haven’t seen my keys anywhere, …………………?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "have you",
                "haven't you",
                "did you"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "3d07894a09294585b8db876ada8c781d"
        }
    ]
}